<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luke Green</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Luke Green</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello, website!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/hello-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/hello-website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Welcome to my website. Over the years, many different sites created by me have lived at this domain. This is the new one, and who knows how long it will be here. It is different from the previous ones, which mostly served as a way to prove to potential employers that I could indeed write code. Now that I have, and have a job :-), this is more to serve as my personal home on the web; although I imagine at some point my resume and some projects I have created will end up here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>About Welcome! Here are some things I am:&#xA;Novice photographer (wildlife primarily) Technically professional software engineer @ Red Hat Passionate home cook Sometimes homebrewer, though I haven&amp;rsquo;t made anything in a while </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternatives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/alternatives/</guid>
      <description>Here are some things I am trying to stop using, why, and what I&amp;rsquo;ve replaced them with; if they should be replaced. Some of them are for health reasons, moral reasons, or privacy reasons. I am not claiming that this is the perfect way to satisfy any of those goals, just what I am working on right now.&#xA;Social Media Instagram In its infancy, Instagram was pretty cool and was a fun way to see photos of what your friends were doing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
